plavid.com 2016-10-31

# About | Plavid

Plavid allows publishers to maximize their ad revenues through **engaging video ads** by Premium brands.  
Over **10.000 publishers** all over the world trust it.  
Join our network to start make money online with **awesome ad formats** that respect your users!

### Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY MOSAICOON S.P.A.**

**Our Services**

Mosaicoon S.p.A. (hereinafter also referred to as “Mosaicoon” or “the Company”) is a leader in the online marketing sector, specialized in creating, designing and distributing advertising campaigns through media channels. 

The company owns the website [www.mosaicoon.com](http://www.mosaicoon.com/), [www.funnected.com](http://funnected.com/), [www.tvapuntate.it](http://www.tvapuntate.it/) (hereinafterjointly referred to as“Website”) as well as online platforms such as [www.plavidnetwork.com](http://www.plavidnetwork.com/) and [creators.mosaicoon.com](http://creators.mosaicoon.com/) (hereinafter individually referred to as “Plavid”,“Mosaicoon Creators”, and jointly referred to as “the Platforms”), through which the Company performs the “Services” described hereinafter.

In particular, the website www.mosaicoon.com allows users (i.e. internet users that visit the company’s website either for private or business-related interests) to know more about the activities and the Services provided by the Company.

By using Plavid, Mosaicoon allows its own users (i.e. besides internet users visiting Plavid, every blogger, editor, publisher and any other user that registers an account on the aforementioned platform) to use the Services and the products provided by the Company in order to publish and share on their own websites, social networks and/or other internet web pages the advertising campaigns created, designed and produced by Mosaicoon for its customers.In relation to the Services concerning the use of the Plavid platform, Mosaicoon also provides its users registered on the platform with the Plavid Advertising Player consisting in both a script and a frame which – once embedded into any user’s website, social network account and/or web page – make possible the visualization of the advertising campaign to the end user of the same (hereinafter also referred to as “ End User of the Campaign”).

By using www.funnected.com, www.tvapuntate.it Mosaicoon allows its own users (i.e. internet users that visitwww.funnected.com, www.tvapuntate.it either for private or business-related interests) to gain knowledge of some of the advertising campaigns produced and distributed by the Company.

By using Mosaicoon Creators, Mosaicoon allows its own users (i.e. internet users visiting Mosaicoon Creators’s website, as well as any other user that registers an account on the aforementioned platform) to upload on the platform the specific creative contents they have realized under the terms and conditions agreed upon with the Company.

In order to better protect and secure the use of the Company’s website and of its platforms, Mosaicoon provides internet users with the following privacy notice (hereinafter also referred to as “Privacy Policy”).

This Privacy Policy applies to “User and Users” exclusively identified as internet users visiting the Company’s website and/or the Platforms as defined above.

In case the User does not agree with the terms and conditions set forth in this Privacy Policy, the User is kindly requested not to visit or use the Company’s website or the Platforms and must refrain from providing personal information. Some of the Services may be subject to personal information authorization.

**MOSAICOON PRIVACY NOTICE**

With regards to the above-mentioned activities, the Company undertakes to protect Users’ privacy and to process their personal data in compliance with the principles of fairness, legality, transparency and confidentiality.

In particular, in accordance with the provisions set out in Legislative Decree no. 196/2003 and subsequent amendments, with this Privacy Policy Mosaicoon intends to provide the Users with all necessary information about the processing of their personal data and the protection of their privacy while using the Services of the Company on the Website or on the Platforms.

The terms and conditions set forth in this privacy notice apply to every website or Platform owned by Mosaicoon, unless otherwise specified in the registration forms provided by the Company to the Users or in different written agreements between the Users and the Company.

This information notice shall not be considered valid for other websites that may be visited via links on the websites under the Mosaicoon’s domain name, which shall not be held liable under any circumstances for the websites of third parties.

**I.  THE DATA CONTROLLER **

The data controller is Mosaicoon S.p.A., with registered offices in Via Nazionale, 42 – 90040 Isola delle Femmine (Pa), and registered in the Company Register of Palermo under no. 05866440828, REA no. 280967, in the person of its legal representative.

Exclusively for the purpose of satisfying organizational and operational needs and in accordance with the provisions set forth by article 29 of the Regulations governing personal data protection (i.e. the above mentioned Legislative Decree no. 196/2003), the Company has recently appointed the following persons as subjects responsible for the processing of personal data, who are domiciled at the Company’s registered offices: 

√ Ms. Teresa Fiasconaro Lima;

√ Mr. Giuseppe Costanza.

Personal data are collected and handled by the above mentioned Data Controllers as well as by other persons possibly in charge of processing personal data, of whom an updated list may be requested by sending an email to [[privacy@mosaicoon.com](mailto:privacy@mosaicoon.com)] or through registered mail to the following address:

Mosaicoon S.p.A., Via Nazionale42– 90040, Isola delle Femmine (PA), Italy  
To the attention of: Giuseppe Costanza

**II.  PLACE WHERE PERSONAL DATA ARE PROCESSED**

All personal data, related to the Services provided by the Company, is processed at the above-mentioned registered offices of the Data Controller. Only in case of need, personal data related to the Services may be processed by third persons in charge of the maintenance of the technological elements of the websites owned by Mosaicoon.

**III.  TYPES OF DATA PROCESSED BY MOSAICOON**

Mosaicoon processes some information and/or personal data related to its Users, that may be processed by the Company while surfing on Mosaicoon’s Website  or during the Users’ registration on Mosaicoon’s Platforms as well as whenever a User submits to the Company a request of payment regarding the Services related to the use of the Platforms.

In particular, Mosaicoon may collect and use the following type of data:

**a)  Users’ data collected while visiting the Company’s website or the online Platforms**

The IT systems and software used, in order to allow for Mosaicoon’s Website, as well as Platforms to operate, collect, during their normal functioning, some personal data which is automatically transmitted when using the Internet. This information is not collected for the purpose of identifying any subjects. However, because of its specific nature, said information could be elaborated and associated with the data held by third parties, thereby allowing for the identification of the Users.

This category of data includes, for example, IP addresses or domain names used by the Users that visit Mosaicoon’s website or log on the Platforms, websites visited by the Users within other websites owned by Mosaicoon, domain names and website addresses used by the Users to access (through referral) Mosaicoon’s website or log on the Platforms, the URI (Uniform Resource Identifier) addresses of the accessed resources, the method used to submit the request to the server, the size of the file obtained in response, the number code indicating the status of the response submitted by the server and other parameters related to the specific type of browser (e.g., Internet Explorer, Firefox) or to the User’s operating system (e.g., Macintosh, Windows, etc.) and IT environment. 

These data are processed, for the time strictly necessary, for the sole purpose of collecting anonymous statistical information relating to the use of the website, and to provide feedback as to its proper operation.Please note that the above-mentioned data may be also used to assess liability in the event of IT crimes committed with damage to Mosaicoon’s Website and/or to Platforms. Except for this case, data collected on the web are preserved and processed in compliance with applicable legislation.

**b)  Personal data provided by Users while or after registering on the Platforms**

Mosaicoon is also entitled to collect and use some information and/or personal data provided by Users on a voluntary basis while registering on Plavid and Mosaicoon Creators.

This information and/or personal data may be provided by Users by filling out specific registration forms (available either online or offline), which may require the User to specify, for example, his/her name, surname, date of birth, gender, tax code, profession, VAT registration number, address, email address, phone number, the URL of the homepage of the website owned by the User or of the social network account of the User in order to subscribe to the Services provided by the Company or requested to the User through the Platforms,the number of bank account or other data necessary for processing the payment requests in favor of the Users.

Personal data provided by the User during or after the registration process are processed by Mosaicoon in compliance with the Regulations governing personal data protection and are used only in order to process the registration on the Platforms and allow the use of Plavid and Mosaicoon Creators and of the related Services for the following purposes. 

**c)  Personal data provided by the User in order to apply as a candidate for Mosaicoon Human resources Department**

Mosaicoon can collect and use some information, and/or personal data provided on the User’s own accord, by filling in a proper data collection form, and/or by sending his/her CV and Portfolio via email to the Company. The Company will collect personal data of “common” nature, such as data usually contained in the CV (personal data, education, occupation, specific skill and expertise, etc.), as well as any further data provided by the User to better describe his/her application. If the User considers it advisable, he/she may provide personal data of “sensitive” nature (such as personal data revealing racial or ethnic, religious, philosophical or other beliefs, political opinions, membership of political parties, unions, associations or organizations of a religious, philosophical, political or trade union, as well as personal data disclosing health and sex life, as specified by art.4, let. d of the Italian Legislative Decree n.196/03), which may be processed only with the prior expressed consent of the User.

**IV.  PURPOSE OF THE PROCESSING OF DATA **

Data provided by Users are processed, depending on their type or category, for some or all of the following purposes:

management of the systems and of the Services required by the User and provided by the Company on the basis of specific agreements signed with the Company and of the legislation in force (e.g. management of Users’ Platform accounts, etc.);

for purposes strictly related to the set up and/or management of a commercial and/or contractual relationship between the User and Mosaicoon (e.g. fulfillment of contractual obligations and execution of operations arising from the contract, administrative and operational management of the relationship, management of the payments to the Users, etc.);

contact the Users, by mail or email, in order to confirm or modify information held by the Company;

provide and manage the technical assistance necessary in order to provide the products and Services related to the use of the online Platforms;

improve the quality and the structure of the Platforms of the Company and develop new services and features relating to the Platforms;

upon prior and informed consent of the Users, send commercial information (e.g. newsletters) concerning promotions, products, new initiatives and/or services provided by the Company.

**V.  NATURE OF THE COLLECTED DATA **

Besides the provisions about net surfing data, the User is free to provide the personal data indicated in the registration forms.

Please note that some of the data required in the above-mentioned forms (i.e., the ones marked by an asterisk *) are functional for the use of Plavid and Mosaicoon Creators and, therefore, are necessarily required by the Company in order to allow access to the Platforms and to the related Services.

Not providing these data will preclude the User from successfully completing the registration on the Platforms and from obtaining the Services requested.  
The provision of personal data in relation to point III lett. c) is optional but hence essential to comply with the specific request of the User for appraisal of his/her application or in   response to a notice published online by the Company.

**VI.   DATA PROCESSING AND SAFETY**

Personal data will be processed through the use of automated instruments (e.g., electronic procedures and devices) for the time strictly necessary to achieve the purposes for which said data were collected (i.e., to supply the Services) and in compliance with applicable legislation.

In compliance with the legislation in force and with the standards on data protection approved for the specific sector of industry, the Company has adopted specific safety measures to prevent the loss of data and the unlawful and/or incorrect use and/or the misuse of data as well as any unauthorized access.

All data is collected and stored by the Company for the time strictly necessary to achieve the purposes for which the data were collected, and are kept in safe areas places with access limited to authorized personnel only.

Specific security measures are adopted to prevent the loss of data and the unlawful and/or incorrect use and/or the misuse of data as well as any unauthorized access.

**VII.  DATA DISCLOSURE AND SHARING**

In order to achieve the above-mentioned purposes and properly fulfill the obligations relating to the service, data may be communicated to third parties and, in particular, to:

a) subsidiaries, associates or affiliate companies;

b) natural and/or legal persons, also outside of the Company, that act as privacy officers appointed by Mosaicoon;

c) natural and/or legal persons, also outside of the Company, that provide services for the management of the information and data system used by Mosaicoon and for the management of telecommunication networks, and that act as privacy officers;

d) professional firms and companies which provide assistance and advice also as regards corporate organization management (e.g., public accountants, administrative, legal, tax and finance consultants);

e) contractual partners of Mosaicoon, service providers to which the data has to be communicated in order to fulfill the obligations relating to the Services;

f) entities and/or government agencies in order to allow for controls and inspections to be carried out in compliance with tax and civil obligations;

g) banks and insurance companies in order to consent the performance of credit and insurance activities;

h) competent authorities for the fulfillment of legal obligations and/or orders in case of specific request of government agencies.

Processed data could also be communicated in case of mergers and acquisitions of the Company and/or of its assets, as well as in the unlikely event of liquidation, bankruptcy or insolvency proceedings, in which cases personal data would be transferred together with other assets.

Users will be informed of similar cases, as described in the following section “Amendments and updates to the Privacy Policy”.

Other than the above cases, processed data will not be communicated or shared with third parties.

**VIII.  USER’S RIGHT TO ACCESS HIS/HER PERSONAL DATA**

The User shall be entitled to exercise his/her rights against the Data Controller in accordance with art. 7 of D.lgs.196/2003.

In particular, the persons to whom personal data refer shall have the right, at any time, to request and obtain confirmation from Mosaicoon as to whether his/her personal data exist or not, regardless of whether they have already been recorded or not, and the right to have these data communicated in an intelligible manner.

The User shall also have the right to be informed of: a) the source of personal data; b) the purpose and methods of the processing; c) the logic applied to the processing, if this is carried out with the help of electronic means; d) the identity of the Data Controller, data processors and of appointed the representative; e) the entities or categories of entity to which personal data may be communicated and with which personal data may be shared in their capacity as appointed representative(s) in the territory of the State, data processor(s) or person(s) in charge of data processing.

The User shall also have the right to: a) request the update, rectification or, upon request, integration of the data; b) request to delete, render anonymous or block data that have been unlawfully processed, including data whose retention is unnecessary with regards to the purposes for which they have been collected or subsequently processed; c) obtain a certificate stating that the operations under letters a) and b) have been notified, also with regards to their contents, to the entities to which the data were communicated or disclosed, unless the fulfillment of this obligation becomes impossible or involves a manifestly disproportionate effort compared to the protected right.

The User shall have the right to object/oppose/resist, in whole or in part to: a) on legitimate grounds, the processing of personal data concerning him/her, even if said data are relevant for the purposes for which they were collected; b) the processing of personal data concerning him/her, when carried out for the purpose of sending advertising or direct sales materials or in order to carry out marketing or commercial surveys.

In order to require the above-mentioned information and/or to exercise the rights arising from article no. 7 of Legislative Decree no. 196/2003, the User can contact Mosaicoon by sending an email to [[privacy@mosaicoon.com](mailto:privacy@mosaicoon.com)] or by sending a request through registered mail to the following address:

√ Mosaicoon S.p.A., Via Nazionale, 42 – CAP 90040 Isola delle Femmine (Pa), Italia

**IX.  COMMUNICATIONS**

The User must promptly inform Mosaicoon of any change or possible mistake related to his/her own personal data and to payment details, specifying whether it is a change or a mistake.

Any communication addressed to the Company must be sent to the above-mentioned address by means of the aforementioned means.

**X.  THIRD PARTY WEBSITES **

Please note that Mosaicoon cannot investigate the contents of websites of third parties and cannot access personal data of any visitors End User of the Campaign or users of the websites or social network accounts of its own Users (hereinafter also referred to as “Consumers”) but only of aggregate and anonymous data used in order to evaluate the performance and efficiency of its own advertising campaigns.   
Among the afore-mentioned aggregate and anonymous data whose possession may be gained by Mosaicoon through the websites, the web pages and/or the social network accounts of its own Users are included, for example, the data related to the number of impressions and/or click/views of the Advertising Campaign collected through the Plavid Advertising Player. In this regard, it has to be specified that Mosaicoon will use the afore-mentioned data in order to evaluate the performances and the effectiveness of the advertising Campaigns realized and/or distributed by Mosaicoon for its clients.

Therefore, the User will remain the sole and exclusive owner and will be the only person responsible for the processing of the personal data of the Consumers. Mosaicoon will never be responsible for processing personal data of any Consumers and shall not be held liable for any prejudices, claims, damages or expenses that may arise from the omission or incorrect processing of said personal data.  
Please note also that the User may find links, on the Website or on the Platforms of the Company, leading to other websites that do not operate under this Privacy Policy. If the User clicks on any link of a third party on the Website, he/she may be redirected to a website that is not controlled by Mosaicoon. These third-party websites may solicit independently and collect information, including User’s personal information and, in some instances, provide Mosaicoon with information about the User’s activity on those websites. Thus, we recommend the User to consult the regulations on privacy of all third-party websites he/she may visit by clicking on the “privacy” link usually located at the bottom of the webpage the you are visiting.

**XI. COOKIE POLICY**

**Mosaicoon, as Holder, expresses this cookie policy to show specifically types and aims of the cookies present on Mosaicoon Websites and Platforms, and to give instructions on how to refuse or delete such cookies, if desired.  **

**Continuing Mosaicoon website navigation (by closing the “short” information banner, by moving through the pages or by clicking on any of its elements), the User agrees to use cookies in accordance with this Cookie Policy.**

**A)  What cookies are and how they are used **

To make navigation easier and more intuitive, Web Sites and Platforms of the Company make use of cookie technology. Cookies are information entered by a web server (eg. Website) to the User’s Internet browser that automatically stores them on the device (PC, tablet, smartphone, etc.) and automatically sends them to the web server at each subsequent access to the website. Such information may be related to the User, his/her preferences or device to access the Internet and are mainly used to adjust the operation of the website or Platforms to the expectations of the User, offering a more personalized browsing experience and memorizing the choices previously made.

By _default_ , almost all web browsers are set to automatically accept cookies. Visitors/Users can still change the default configuration, as best illustrated below in this very same Policy.

Some cookies are necessary for the proper provision of the Web sites or Platforms, useful for their personalized fruition; in this case, their inhibition could compromise some functionalities of the website.

**B) Types of Cookies**

• “ **Session cookies** ” **:** these cookies are stored on the User’s computer for purely technical and functional requirements, for the transmission of session identifiers required to enable a safe and efficient navigation of the website; they are deleted when closing the browser. This type of cookie avoids the use of other technologies that could compromise the privacy of the navigation of the users;

• “ **Persistent cookies** ” **:** these cookies are stored on the device of the User until their expiry or cancellation from the User. Through persistent cookies visitors accessing the website are automatically recognized at each visit. They are used to facilitate navigation within the website and its correct use, to facilitate access to services that require authentication (avoiding users to re-enter authentication credentials for each access to services), for statistical purposes, to know which areas of the website have been visited, as well as, in some cases, for the optimal management of pages and advertising spaces or to deliver contents and advertisings in line with the choices made by surfers.

Queste due tipologie di cookie (di sessione e persistenti) possono a loro volta essere:

• “ **first party** ” cookies, when they are managed directly by the owner and/or manager of the website;

• “ **third party** ” cookies, when they are set up and managed by foreign managers to the website visited by the User.

**C)  Main purposes of cookies**

**TECHNICAL COOKIES:** those cookies necessary to allow website navigation and the use of certain products and services. They are used, for example, to recognize the user that has logged into his/her mailbox and to keep the session open, even when he/she visits other pages of the website, or to ensure some security measures of the website and monitor their operation.

**ANALYTICS COOKIES:** those cookies that allow to collect data on the User’s use of the Company website or Platforms – including the elements on which you click while browsing, the time spent on the website or on the Platforms of the Company , the number of visitors – in order to improve the performance and design of the website itself or the Platforms or for statistical purposes. All information gathered by these cookies is anonymous and not linked to the User’s personal data. These cookies may be shared with third parties, legal entities and/or individuals, even outside the Company, providing services for the management of the information system used by Mosaicoon or analysis tools. However, this type of cookie is used only for purposes related to the website or to the platforms of the Company.  

**PREFERENCES COOKIES:** those cookies than enable the website to remember the choices made by the User (such as name, language, country of origin, etc.) and provide customized advanced features.   

**COOKIES OF SOCIAL NETWORK:** these cookies enable the User to share even with other users the contents of the website he/she is visiting or to express his/her opinion about. Those cookies are typically used to activate the “Like” or “Follow” of social networks such as Facebook and Twitter, to name a few. These services are mainly provided by outside suppliers. If you have an account or if you use the services of such persons on other websites, these websites may be able to know that the User has visited the website or the Platforms of Mosaicoon. The use of data collected from these external operators through cookies is subject to their respective privacy policies, which, therefore, we recommend you to consult in order to know the purposes and methods of processing of personal data carried out by them.  

**ADVERTISING COOKIES** : those cookies used to advertise within a website. Some of them are used to calculate the value of the advertising offer, to identify individual advertisements and to know which one has been selected and when. Other advertising cookies, such as behavioral and retargeting cookies are used to deduce the “profile” of the User and to offer later him/her advertisements in line with his/her behavior on the network (thus outside of the websites of Mosaicoon) and presumably in line with the interests manifested. This “profile” is anonymous and the information collected by these cookies does not permit to trace the User’s identity. The advertising services are mainly provided by outside suppliers. The use of the data collected by these external operators through cookies is subject to their privacy policies and thus those cookies are identified with the names of the individuals listed in the table below.   

**D)  List and managing of cookies present on the websites and Platforms of Mosaicoon**

The following tables show the list of those cookies present on each website or platform of Mosaicoon and the method of selection of preferences.   

Apart from those cookies managed directly by the Company (First Party Cookies ), the websites and platforms of Mosaicoon may use third-party cookies, including cookies of the most popular Social Networks (Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Google plus, etc ..)

Third-party cookies (as well as social networks cookies) fall under the direct and exclusive responsibility of the same operator. These cookies are not directly controllable by Mosaicoon, which cannot hence guarantee the use that third parties/owners make of the information collected. More information about privacy and their use are available directly on the websites of the respective managers; to easily manage third-party cookies we suggest you to refer to the website of  [Your Online Choices](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/ch-it). This website allows, in fact, to find out which cookies are enabled on your computer, indicating the name of the company that produces and/or manages them.

### Website: Mosaicoon.com

Company | Service | Type | Link information and management preferences  
---|---|---|---  
Mosaicoon | Analytics | first party |    
Mosaicoon | preferenze sui cookie | first party |    
Facebook | Funzioni di condivisione social | third party | <https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>  
Google | Funzioni di condivisione social, videoplayer Youtube, analytics | third party | [Google Cookie Technologies](http://www.google.com/intl/it_it/policies/technologies/cookies/)  
Twitter | Funzioni di condivisione social | third party | [Twitter Cookie Technologies](https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170519-uso-dei-cookie-e-di-altre-tecnologie-simili-da-parte-di-twitter)  
Linkedin | Funzioni di condivisione social | third party | [Linkedin Cookie Technologies](http://it.linkedin.com/legal/cookie-policy)  
  
### Website: Plavidnetwork.com

Company | Service | Type | Link information and management preferences  
---|---|---|---  
Mosaicoon | Analytics | first party |    
Mosaicoon | preferenze sui cookie | first party |    
Facebook | Funzioni di condivisione social | third party | <https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>  
Google | DFP | third party | [Google Ads Technologies](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)  
Google | Funzioni di condivisione social, videoplayer Youtube, analytics | third party | [Google Cookie Technologies](http://www.google.com/intl/it_it/policies/technologies/cookies/)  
Twitter | Funzioni di condivisione social | third party | [Twitter Cookie Technologies](https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170519-uso-dei-cookie-e-di-altre-tecnologie-simili-da-parte-di-twitter)  
Linkedin | Funzioni di condivisione social | third party | [Linkedin Cookie Technologies](http://it.linkedin.com/legal/cookie-policy)  
Disqus | Funzioni per commenti | third party | [Disqus Cookie Technologies](https://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/466235-use-of-cookies)  
  
### Website: Creators.mosaicoon.com

Company | Service | Type | Link information and management preferences  
---|---|---|---  
Mosaicoon | Analytics | first party |    
Mosaicoon | preferenze sui cookie | first party |    
Facebook | Funzioni di condivisione social | third party | <https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>  
Google | Funzioni di condivisione social, videoplayer Youtube, analytics | third party | [Google Cookie Technologies](http://www.google.com/intl/it_it/policies/technologies/cookies/)  
Twitter | Funzioni di condivisione social | third party | [Twitter Cookie Technologies](https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170519-uso-dei-cookie-e-di-altre-tecnologie-simili-da-parte-di-twitter)  
Linkedin | Funzioni di condivisione social | third party | [Linkedin Cookie Technologies](http://it.linkedin.com/legal/cookie-policy)  
Disqus | Funzioni per commenti | third party | [Disqus Cookie Technologies](https://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/466235-use-of-cookies)  
Vimeo | Videoplayer Vimeo | third party | [Vimeo Cookie Technologies](https://vimeo.com/cookie_policy)  
  
### Website: Tvapuntate.it

Company | Service | Type | Link information and management preferences  
---|---|---|---  
Mosaicoon | Analytics | first party |    
Mosaicoon | preferenze sui cookie | first party |    
Mosaicoon | Plavid advertising videoplayer | first party | [Plavid Cookie Technologies](https://plavidnetwork.com/cookie-policy-third-parts/)  
Facebook | Funzioni di condivisione social | third party | <https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>  
Google | Funzioni di condivisione social, videoplayer Youtube, analytics | third party | [Google Cookie Technologies](http://www.google.com/intl/it_it/policies/technologies/cookies/)  
Twitter | Funzioni di condivisione social | third party | [Twitter Cookie Technologies](https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170519-uso-dei-cookie-e-di-altre-tecnologie-simili-da-parte-di-twitter)  
Vimeo | Videoplayer Vimeo | third party | [Vimeo Cookie Technologies](https://vimeo.com/cookie_policy)  
Adform | Advertising, Content Serving and Web Analytics Technology | third party | [Adform Cookie Technologies](http://site.adform.com/privacy-policy/en/)  
  
### Website: Funnected.com

Company | Service | Type | Link information and management preferences  
---|---|---|---  
Mosaicoon | Analytics | first party |    
Mosaicoon | preferenze sui cookie | first party |    
Mosaicoon | Plavid advertising videoplayer | first party | [Plavid Cookie Technologies](https://plavidnetwork.com/cookie-policy-third-parts/)  
Facebook | Funzioni di condivisione social | third party | <https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>  
Google | Funzioni di condivisione social, videoplayer Youtube, analytics | third party | [Google Cookie Technologies](http://www.google.com/intl/it_it/policies/technologies/cookies/)  
Twitter | Funzioni di condivisione social | third party | [Twitter Cookie Technologies](https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170519-uso-dei-cookie-e-di-altre-tecnologie-simili-da-parte-di-twitter)  
Vimeo | Videoplayer Vimeo | third party | [Vimeo Cookie Technologies](https://vimeo.com/cookie_policy)  
Pinterest | Funzioni di condivisione social | third party | [Pinterest Cookie Technologies](https://about.pinterest.com/it/privacy-policy)  
  
**E)  Cookies management by browser **

The User has the possibility to remove existing cookies and block the installation of new cookies by browser settings. Please note that by disabling all cookies, Mosaicoon Websites and Platforms operation may be compromised. If the User/Visitor wants to decide in each situation whether to accept cookies or not, he/she can set the browser to notify each time a cookies is saved.

For more detailed information on the procedure required, please consult the guide of the browser used by the User. The instructions of the widely used browses are indicated below: 

**Google Chrome**

To know how change your cookie’s preferences through this browser:<http://www.google.it/intl/it/policies/technologies/managing/>. 

To know how to turn on the incognito mode: <https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95464?hl=it>.

To know how to delete cookies, block them possibly selectively, to receive alerts on your cookie settings: <https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=it>.

**Firefox**

To know how change your cookie’s preferences through this browser: [https://support.mozilla.org/it/kb/Gestione%20dei%20cookie](https://support.mozilla.org/it/kb/gestione%252525252520dei%252525252520cookie).

To know how to manage privacy settings panel and inhibit tracking your online activities: [https://support.mozilla.org/it/kb/Impostazioni%20di%20Firefox%20-%20pannello%20Privacy](https://support.mozilla.org/it/kb/impostazioni%252525252520di%252525252520firefox%252525252520-%252525252520pannello%252525252520privacy).

To know how enable and disable cookies: [https://support.mozilla.org/it/kb/Attivare%20e%20disattivare%20i%20cookie](https://support.mozilla.org/it/kb/attivare%252525252520e%252525252520disattivare%252525252520i%252525252520cookie).

To know how remove cookies: [https://support.mozilla.org/it/kb/Eliminare%20i%20cookie](https://support.mozilla.org/it/kb/eliminare%252525252520i%252525252520cookie).

To know how block cookies: [https://support.mozilla.org/it/kb/Bloccare%20i%20cookie](https://support.mozilla.org/it/kb/bloccare%252525252520i%252525252520cookie).

To know deactivate only third-party cookies: [https://support.mozilla.org/it/kb/Disattivare%20i%20cookie%20di%20terze%20parti](https://support.mozilla.org/it/kb/disattivare%252525252520i%252525252520cookie%252525252520di%252525252520terze%252525252520parti).

**Internet Explorer**

To know how change your cookie’s preferences through this browser: <http://windows.microsoft.com/it-it/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies#ie=ie-11-win-7>.

**Safari**

To know how change your cookie’s preferences through this browser: <http://supporto.teletu.it/assistenza-tecnica/configurazioni/browser-internet/safari/gestione-cookie/>.

**Opera**

To know how change your cookie’s preferences through this browser: [http://help.opera.com/Windows/10.00/it/cookies.html](http://help.opera.com/windows/10.00/it/cookies.html).

**XII**. **PERIODICAL AMENDMENTS AND/OR UPDATES PRIVACY POLICY**

This document contains the “Privacy Policy” of Mosaicoon and will be subject to periodical amendments and/or updates. Such amendments and updates will be communicated to Users on the websites and on the Platforms of Mosaicoon.

**Last Update  29/05/2015 **
